menuism.com 2008-05-09

# Privacy | menuism

**Effective Date: 9/1/2006**   

**Two Bit Operation Privacy Notice**   

This website is owned and operated by Two Bit Operation. This privacy notice explains what information is collected from those who visit their website, and how that information is used, disclosed, and protected. This notice applies solely to information collected from this website.   

**What types of information are collected from users?**   

**Personally identifiable information:** information that is directly identifiable with a specific person, such as name, address, phone number, email address, location, screenname, network or online activities.   

Two Bit Operation will not collect information from minors under 13 without parental consent, in accordance with the Child Online Privacy Protection Act.

**Aggregate and non-personal information:**

**Cookies:** Like many companies, we use "cookies" on our website. Cookies are bits of text that are placed on your computer's hard drive when you visit certain websites. Cookies may enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular site.   

When you visit our website, cookies are placed on your computer. We use cookies to tell us, for example, whether you've visited us before or if you're a new visitor and to help us identify site features which you may have the greatest interest. We collect this information to enhance your experience on our website. We may use cookies in general to collect information to determine how to improve our sites by seeing which areas, features, and products are most popular; to personalize the site and make recommendations based on products you have liked in the past as well as to improve the site experience; and to complete transactions you have requested. Advertisers that serve ads on our Web sites may also use their own cookies.

**Javascript:** Certain pages on our site contain javascript which allows third parties to obtain information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the javascript appears, the URL of the page on which the javascript appears, the time the page containing the javascript was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page, and the information in cookies set by the third party.

Two Bit Operation uses third-party advertising companies that utilize javascript to collect certain anonymous information about an Internet user's visit to our Web site. This allows companies to better understand the traffic patterns within their Web sites and recognize visitors generated from online and e-mail advertising campaigns. They also allow advertisers to understand the response patterns in online advertising.

**How and when is personally identifiable information collected?**   

We collect information when you sign up, use, or request information about our services, or otherwise communicate with Two Bit Operation via Internet or other wireless device. Some information is automatically collected whenever you interact with Two Bit Operation's website, such as IP address and the type of browser you use. We may also receive information about you from other sources such as credit or marketing information.   

In general, we use "personally identifiable" information to market and provide services, to anticipate and resolve problems with your service, or to create and inform you of services that better meet your needs. For example, by understanding how you use our Web site, we are able to customize and personalize your experience or we may be able to provide information we think will interest you or enable you to conduct transactions more easily.   

**How do we use personally identifiable information?**

We may use the information you provide to contact you from time to time. For example, we may (i) send you promotional materials and other communications you request, (ii) respond to your comments or questions, or (iii) contact you if needed while processing a product or service you requested through our website. We also may use the information you provide to contact you for your opinions on Two Bit Operation products or the website.

We also use personally-identifiable information about you to improve our website features and content and to analyze website usage. In addition, we use personally-identifiable information for market research purposes. We also may use personally-identifiable information about you to deliver content that is customized to your interests as we understand them from the information you've provided to us and your activities on the site.

Your screenname, personal icon, and any reviews or comments you submit will also be displayed on your personal profile page, and individual restaurant review pages. If you include personally-identifiable information in your screenname, personal icon, reviews or comments, or other information displayed on your personal profile page, then you are consenting to allow that information to be displayed on the website.

**How do we share personally identifiable information?**

Two Bit Operation is NOT in the business of selling personally identifiable information to others and we disclose "personally identifiable" information only in the following ways: 

**With your consent:** We may obtain your consent to disclose personally identifiable information in a number ways, including in writing; verbally; online by clicking a button; through the use of a dialing string or button on a wireless device or handset; or at the time of initiation or use of any service when your consent is part of the required terms and conditions to use the service. Sometimes your consent is implicit. For example, if you purchase a product through our Web site and request that it be shipped to your home, you implicitly consent to our disclosure of your name and address to a third-party shipping company to complete delivery and your charge card number to the bank to collect payment. 

**Transaction processing:** We disclose personally identifiable information to third parties as necessary to complete a transaction or perform a service in our behalf. When the third party acts solely in our behalf, such as a billing service vendor, Two Bit Operation will restrict their use and disclosure of personally identifiable information. That means that such third party, acting solely on our behalf, will not be permitted to disclose "personally identifiable" information to another third party without your consent. 

Our services may let you take advantage of services and products offered by other companies. In those cases, information about you received by those third parties will be governed by their privacy policies. 

**Business transfers:** In the event that Two Bit Operation is involved in a merger, acquisition, insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership, personally identifiable customer information may be transferred as one of the business assets in the transaction.

**Information released in compliance with the law:** We release personally identifiable and other account information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law (e.g., a lawful subpoena, E-9-1-1 information); to enforce or apply our customer agreements; to initiate, render, bill, and collect for services; or to protect our rights or property, or to protect users of those services and other carriers from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of, or subscription to, such services; or if we reasonably believe that an emergency involving immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to any person requires disclosure of communications or justifies disclosure of records without delay. 

**How do we protect personally identifiable information?**   

The security of personally-identifiable information is important to us. We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against unauthorized use, disclosure, alteration or destruction of the personally-identifiable information we collect on this website.   

**How do we share aggregate and non-personal information?**   

We sell aggregate and non-personal information about customer activity and opinions as a market research service to restaurants or any other parties interested in the data. The data will be anonymous, so personally identifiable information will not be included in that research.   

**Updates to this privacy notice:**

We may change or update portions of this privacy notice at any time. Please review these terms regularly so you are aware of any changes or updates to the notice. We will indicate the notice's effective date on the first page of the notice.
